

COURSES FROM EDUCATION

- HTML & CSS
- JavaScript Frontend
- JavaScript Backend
- C#
- Data Storage
- ASP.NET
- CMS

The education also includes work with agile methodology and security.

OTHER STUDIES

I am also studying Wordpress development and PHP.

OTHER SKILLS

- Graphic design and image editing
- 3D modeling and CAD
- 3D printing and 3D printers
- Computer graphics and animation film production

"Veronica has handled all her tasks very well and has been highly appreciated by both customers and colleagues. With her positive attitude and cheerful demeanor, she has enriched us."

Peter Johansson, CEO. StädSpecialisten i Närke AB.

// CONTACT INFORMATION

Veronica Axelsson Bondegatan 12, 70225 Örebro 070 - 486 38 52 veronica.axelsson@vea-art.com

LinkedIn: vea-art

GitHub: Veronica-Axelsson

Web Developer & Designer

WORK EXPERIENCE

.NET Developer Internship

EPN Sverige AB | Nov 2023 - May 2024

Nursing Assistant at Gustavsviks Home Care

Örebro Municipality | July 2023 - Aug 2023

Nursing Assistant at Gustavsviks Home Care

Örebro Municipality | Sep 2021 – Aug 2022

Care Assistant at Gustavsviks Home Care

Örebro Municipality | May 2017 – Aug 2021

Intern in 3D Modeling

3D Creators, Sundbyberg | May 2015 - Aug 2015

- 3D modeling and CAD,
- 3D scanning and 3D printing.

EDUCATION

Higher Vocational Education: Web Developer .NET

EC Education | Aug 2022 - May 2024

Google Developer Challenge Scholarship: Front-

end Web Development

Udacity | 2017 - 2018

Graphic Design

Lynda.com | 2016 - 2016

Computer Graphics and Animation.

Bachelor's Degree.

Uppsala University | 2010 - 2014

DRIVING LICENSE

Holder of B driving license.

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Swedish - Native. English - Very good.